<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts | Qi Liu's Homepage</title><link>https://example.com/post/</link><atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Posts</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:50:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Posts</title><link>https://example.com/post/</link></image><item><title>Student Recruitment</title><link>https://example.com/post/recruitment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/post/recruitment/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have multiple fully-funded PhD, MPhil, Postdoc, RA, and intern positions at the University of Hong Kong. &lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="goal-and-style">Goal and Style&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>The goal of research is to generate knowledge and train new researchers. I have worked with a few amazing researchers and mentors and I do believe in the power of advising. I hope to build a close-knit and focused group, where I value one-on-one meetings with group members and team collaboration. The prime motivation for publishing papers is to provide insights and make real-world impact. Eventually, I hope my students can develop their own research tastes and pursue their research agenda independently. &lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="ongoing-projects">Ongoing Projects&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>My research interests include natural language processing and machine learning. I value real-world applications. Here are some ongoing projects in my research group. &lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Natural language processing: large language models and data-centric AI (e.g. data quality and synthetic data generation).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>AI for finance: financial NLP and AI for blockchain/web3.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>AI for science: sequential models (e.g. transformer) and relational models (e.g. graph neural networks) for proteins and molecules.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h4 id="documents">Documents&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>To get to know applicants better, please send the following documents to me. I will read every application carefully. Due to the volume of emails, I am sorry that I cannot respond to every email.&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>CV.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Transcripts.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Research proposal.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Selected publications (if any).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Github (if any).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>TOEFL/GRE/IELTS (if any).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item></channel></rss>